http://www.albertaballet.com/privacy-policy

FAQ
Privacy PolicyAlberta Ballet recognizes and respects the privacy of each visitor to the Alberta Ballet website and each performance. This Privacy Policy explains Alberta Ballet’s treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on or related to Alberta Ballet. We believe in giving you full disclosure about the kinds of information we gather and what we do with it, and in giving you a choice about the use of your personal information. Alberta Ballet reserves the right to alter our privacy principles as business needs require. Any alterations to these principles will be posted on our website in a timely manner. PERSONAL INFORMATION Alberta Ballet collects personal information when you make a purchase or a contribution, register as a patron, request information on our products and services, participate in a promotion or an online survey, contact Alberta Ballet with a question or suggestion, enter contests, or attend special events. Depending on the nature of your interaction with us, we may ask you for information such as your name, phone number, physical address, employment information, email address, credit card information including expiration date and billing address, and product preferences.Your personal information may be used by us (or third parties engaged by us) to: (1) customize the advertising and the content that you see, (2) fulfill your requests for products and services, (3) contact you, (4) conduct research, (5) respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, and (6) establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We will never sell your information to any other third party. Personally identifiable information used for marketing purposes will always be presented as anonymous, aggregate data. No individual will be singled out.Alberta Ballet will from time to time conduct voluntary surveys of visitors to the site to obtain demographic information about them. Such information may be compiled and shared in an anonymous, aggregate format, with advertisers and other third parties, but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals. If you provide your email address, Alberta Ballet may contact you periodically with special offers, updated information and new services. Any emails sent to you by Alberta Ballet offer you the option to be removed from the email mailing list. ANONYMOUS INFORMATIONTypes of non-personally identifiable information include IP addresses, browser Information, advertising Information, and cookies. All anonymous information is used only to measure site activity and to develop ideas for improving our sites. So, when you come back to visit us again, we can tailor information to suit your individual preferences. We use anonymous information to customize information for our users and to help us display information in the best format for you. The goal is to save you time and provide you with a more meaningful visit. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITESOur websites will link to other websites and services from time to time. Alberta Ballet will always attempt to associate with only the most trustworthy partners who share our high standards regarding privacy. Nevertheless, we are not responsible for the content of and privacy practices of any other companies or websites. SECURITY & DISCLAIMERSecurity of your personably identifiable information is of prime importance to all of us at Alberta Ballet. Access to this information is limited and will be used according to the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act. Although we use security that we believe to be appropriate to protect your personal information, we do not guarantee that our security precautions will protect against, and we expressly disclaim any liability for, any loss, misuse, or alteration of your personal information.Inquiries about the privacy policy and/or the use of images photographed at any of our events may be directed to Alberta Ballet’s Privacy Officer at info@albertaballet.com.
